<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Bear With A Bike And A Baby</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Bear With A Bike And A Baby</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:35:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Don&#39;t Have ADHD, I&#39;m Just Lazy (…or so I thought)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/just_lazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/just_lazy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/ADHDUK/comments/1loaowh/spent_years_thinking_i_was_making_excuses_i/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/galleries/audhd/making_excuses.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my experience too, I&amp;rsquo;m not diagnosed but I&amp;rsquo;m beginning the process through my GP who has given me a referral to &lt;a href=&#34;https:/theowl.org&#34;&gt;The Owl Centre&lt;/a&gt;.  It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until our counsellor mentioned it and ran me through some of the &amp;lsquo;symptoms&amp;rsquo; of Autism and ADHD (AuDHD) and then me reading articles and peoples&amp;rsquo; real-life experiences that I&amp;rsquo;ve realised that it is most certainly something I have, even if I don&amp;rsquo;t get a formal diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/remy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/remy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, Eleanor had the miscarrage at the hospital, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I can say about it to be honest.  It was hard, I shut-down and burried myself in the laptop whilst Eleanor was going through it.  I just didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t take it on, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t fix it, I froze, I burried myself into something I &lt;strong&gt;could&lt;/strong&gt; control and fix and I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed of myself for that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Didn&#39;t Even Have A Heartbeat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/no-heatbeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/no-heatbeat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We had our scan yeaterday and found out for certain that our little one didn&amp;rsquo;t progress any futher than just over 5 weeks.  The news we were dreadding came crashing into our hearts and became a reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think over the days leading up to the scan, I had finally accepted the more likely answer that we had lost the baby so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a surprised.  I watched the screen as the sonographer zoomed in, and measured and I see that there was hardly anything there so when she turned to us and uttered the words we were dredding to hear &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Hope, Maybe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hope-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hope-maybe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, we may have some hope - after talking to some friends, we think there may be some reason to hope that the worst hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened.  Many people have said that a baby can quite possibly measure small at this stage, that people have had similar news from this specific group as they&amp;rsquo;re private rather than NHS meaning anyone can operate the equiment without the specific and in-depth training required by the NHS, that ME/CFS can impact the speed of growth, and more importantly  Eleanor is still very much experiencing symptoms and has show no sign of having lost the baby so we wait.  And so we wait, wait, wait for just under one more week, it&amp;rsquo;s been the longest two weeks ever full of ups and downs. Also, being the person I am, I look at how many people we know have lost a baby recently and the statistics are in our favour, but I also know that doen&amp;rsquo;t really mean anything - you can make statistics say anything, but I&amp;rsquo;m clinging to the maths.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inconclusive Scan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/inconclusive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/inconclusive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, we had our scan just over an hour ago and what we thought would be an 8 week embryo, was just 5 weeks.  There&amp;rsquo;s no way this is a miscalculation on our part because Eleanor is regular, and because she&amp;rsquo;s had pregnancy symptoms for the whole 8 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re devistated and having an hour long drive home was full of numbness, sighs and me beign on auto-pilot the whole way home.  We have a midwife appointment tomorrow which was supposed to be our &amp;lsquo;Booking&amp;rsquo; appointment where we register and &amp;lsquo;Book In&amp;rsquo; with the midwife, talk about our medica histories and get into the system, Eleanor has called them so they&amp;rsquo;re aware of our situation and can change the appointment as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Window To The Womb</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/window-to-the-womb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/window-to-the-womb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, today we get to see our little one for the first time.  We decided to have an 8 week scan, just to make sure everything is okay and to see how many we&amp;rsquo;re having as our risk of multiple births is quite high to due my wife&amp;rsquo;s age.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to see our little one, but it&amp;rsquo;s mixed with some apprehension - this is technically called a &amp;lsquo;Viability Scan&amp;rsquo; which is part of what we want to see - we need to be sure that our little one is okay.  We&amp;rsquo;ve known we&amp;rsquo;ve been pregnant for pretty much the whole 8 weeks as Eleanor had symptoms from almost &amp;lsquo;Day 1&amp;rsquo; and Eleanor is still experiencing symptoms but we just want to check - we&amp;rsquo;ve had one friend who recently had a miscarrage and another with a &amp;lsquo;missed&amp;rsquo; miscarrage so we want to be super-sure things are as they should be at this early stage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Having A Baby!!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It started with Eleanor not feeling great for a few days straight and someone at her work suggested that she may be pregnant.  We HAD been trying but it was waaaay too soon for her to be having any symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The thing is, it&amp;rsquo;s crazy how long you need to wait until any kind of medical advice. We thought you&amp;rsquo;d need to book in with a doctor, get connected to a midwife, arrange a scan.  Nope!  None of that until 8  weeks.  We thought we&amp;rsquo;d at least be given an &amp;lsquo;official&amp;rsquo; pregnancy test rather than relying on weeing on a stick (4 times!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
